Clément Tamines PhD Student in Computer Science

☑ clement.tamines@umons.ac.be

informatique.umons.ac.be/staff/Tamines.Clement



I am a PhD student in the Computer Science department at the University of Mons (UMONS) in Belgium. I am co-supervised by Véronique Bruyère (UMONS) and Jean-François Raskin (Université libre de Bruxelles). My research interests regard equilibria in non zero-sum multiplayer games and solving parity and generalized parity games. I am also very interested in the field of machine learning.

Education

2019 - 2020	University	Certificate,	Artificial	Intelligence,	University of	Mons, Belgium.
-------------	------------	--------------	------------	---------------	---------------	----------------

2018 – 2022 PhD in Science, Computer Science, University of Mons, Belgium.

2016 – 2018 **Master of Science**, *Computer Science*, University of Mons, Belgium. Graduated *Summa Cum Laude*.

2013 – 2016 **Bachelor of Science**, *Computer Science*, University of Mons, Belgium. Graduated *Cum Laude*.

Research experience

2018 - 2022 **PhD thesis**

Title Equilibria in multiplayer games with multiple objectives.

Directors Véronique Bruyère & Jean-François Raskin

2017 – 2018 **Master's thesis**

Title Solving generalized parity games.

Director Véronique Bruyère

2016 - 2017 **Master's project**

Title Solving parity games.

Directors Véronique Bruyère & Quentin Hautem

Teaching

2018 – 2020 Teaching assistant, UMONS.

Algorithmics and Bioinformatics (30h).

2019 **Co-supervisor**, *UMONS*.

Introduction to research internship of Victor Dheur on symbolic solving of parity games.

2018 – 2019 **Co-supervisor**, *UMONS*.

o Master's project of Dorian Labeeuw on window techniques for solving parity games.

2016 - 2018 Student teaching assistant, UMONS.

- Programming and algorithmics I (Python 3).
- o Programming and algorithmics II (Java 8).

Publications

- [BPRT19a] Véronique Bruyère, Guillermo A. Pérez, Jean-François Raskin, and Clément Tamines. Partial solvers for generalized parity games. In *Reachability Problems 13th International Conference, RP 2019, Brussels, Belgium, September 11-13, 2019, Proceedings*, pages 63–78, 2019.
- [BPRT19b] Véronique Bruyère, Guillermo A. Pérez, Jean-François Raskin, and Clément Tamines. Partial solvers for generalized parity games. *CoRR*, abs/1907.06913, 2019.

Talks

Partial Solvers for Generalized Parity Games, Highlights'19, 18/09, Warsaw, Poland.
 Partial Solvers for Generalized Parity Games, RP'19, 11/09, Brussels, Belgium.
 Partial Solvers for Generalized Parity Games, MoRe'19, 22/06, Vancouver, Canada.
 Your Turn to Play!, Math & Science Days'19, 29/03, Mons, Belgium.

Attended research events

- 2020 **Dynamics and Information Workshop**, Tel Aviv, Israel.
- 2019 Highlights of Logic, Games and Automata, Warsaw, Poland.

13th International Conference on Reachability Problems, Brussels, Belgium.

LearnAut: Learning and Automata (LICS'19 workshop), Vancouver, Canada.

MoRe: Multi-objective Reasoning in Verification and Synthesis , Vancouver, Canada.

Theory and Algorithms in Graph and Stochastic Games, co-organizer, Mons, Belgium.

MdC: Mardi des Chercheurs (UMONS research event), Mons, Belgium.

CFV Seminar, Brussels, Belgium.

MFV Seminar, Brussels, Belgium.

2018 Highlights of Logic, Games and Automata, Berlin, Germany.

Logic and learning, FoPSS summer school, Oxford, UK.

Modelling and Verification of Parallel Processes, MOVEP summer school, Cachan, France.